Royalty is relative
A Merry Scottish Christmas is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Dustin Rikert.
When estranged siblings Lindsay and Brad travel to Scotland at Christmas to
reunite with their mother Jo, a big family secret is revealed.
Lindsay Morgan, played by Lacey Chabert.
Brad Morgan, played by Scott Wolf.
Mac Bell, played by James Robinson.
Sarah Morgan, played by Kellie Blaise.
Josephine, played by Fiona Bell.
Graeme Stewart, played by Gerry O'Brien.
Joyeux Noël means Merry Christmas in French.
For other uses, see Christmas (disambiguation) and Merry Christmas (disambiguation)
Joyeux Noël (English: Merry Christmas) is a 2005 war
drama film based on the Christmas truce of December 1914, depicted through the eyes of French, Scottish, and German soldiers.
It was written and directed by Christian Carion, and screened out
of competition at the 2005 Cannes Film Festival.
The film, which includes one of the last appearances of Ian Richardson before his death,
was nominated for Best Foreign Language Film at the 78th Academy Awards.
It is a fictionalised account of an actual event that took place in December 1914, when Wilhelm, German Crown
Prince, sent the lead singer of the Berlin Imperial Opera company on a solo visit to the front line.
Singing by the tenor, Walter Kirchhoff, to the 120th and 124th Württemberg
regiments led Scottish soldiers in their trenches to stand up and applaud.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.